Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
Erotic, unpleasant, heavy on the disgust.
Spending time in front of haters makes my heart fall.
No one is my friend, and then another friend.
I'm just tired of going through two or three.
I'm sure that once upon a time...
I'm sure I wasn't like this once.
You weren't like this.
I was just fine, having a good time.
I was the girl of your dreams, the girl of your dreams, the girl of your future
Nostalgic days when hard work brought results
The days when I felt like I could make anything come true
Tsurugi
Yes, healing
I'm not looking for anything extravagant, just be me
I can watch a video and see that and that and that.
I'm just consuming time.
I know that the sooner the better
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love
of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people
Some
The happier I get, the harder it feels
All of my tears are transparent
One for each eye
Let's just say my mind
Inside me, it's all transparent
When I was a child
When I was a little girl
I'll never be more than a child
More of me will be erased...
I pretended not to notice
Flip, flip, flip
In my tears, they're all transparent
I'm really honest
Let's just say my mind
Inside me, it's all transparent
When I was in love for the first time in my life
As it was when I was in love for the first time
I beg you.
Hallo! This time we have Sakura Oda from Morning Musume。 24 and Mariaki Makino from Morning Musume。 24.
This time I'll be talking with Sakura Oda and Mariaki Makino, both from Morning Musume。
Please bear with us until the end.
Please stay with us until the end.
At the beginning of this article, we'll introduce you to the Halloween Project 2024 Summer All Above. Project 2024 Summer All of Us Beggars.
Project 2024 Summer All of Asbeger, which is included in the new single released today.
Project 2024 Summer All of Us Beggar, a live video of the song "Somewhat Sentimental Moments.
Hello.
This song is really a very unique song for Morning Musume。 It's a very unique song for Morning Musume。
I'd like to talk a little about what I pay attention to when I perform it.
I myself usually perform live with a focus on how to involve the audience in the performance.
But for this song, I'm thinking about how I can make the audience see something that is complete in my world.
It's a totally different way of thinking than usual.
The introduction is in a completely different key than the intro, and Akira Yamazaki sings it every time.
As for the dancing, this time there is a part where the dancers dance lying down on the floor.
So I was a little scared at the beginning of each performance.
For the music video, the floor was a little fluffy, so I could do what I practiced, but for the concert, I had to wear concert shoes with heels and I had to be careful with the microphone.
But in a café, it's difficult to roll over in the audience, but I finally got the hang of it.
But I finally got the hang of it and realized that it's important to go all out.
I've recently learned that it's better to go all the way because it's no good if you're a little scared.
I'll talk more about the new single in the second half of the show.
Morning Musume。 24 Concert Tour Autumn WinCan Dance
This is Yumi Ishida's last tour since she's graduating.
The most extended corner of многие people is Tezim, with one side of the tympanum extending to estailo
The core of the tour is definitely Mr. White Sea, so I'm wondering if we'll be able to see a lot of Ishida's style in this tour.
I'm sure that we'll be able to see a lot of Ishida-san's style in this tour.
I want to absorb more and more of what I can steal from him on this tour.
I would like to make this tour to observe Mr. Ishida again.
Please take a look at this video.
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyabi.
I'm Riai Matsunaga of Juice Juice!
Ganbari Nasubi.
Yes, this time...
I'd like to make a chilled pasta with peaches and prosciutto ham.
Yay, yay!
So, Riai, do you usually cook?
I don't cook at all.
I can't cook at all.
Yes, yes, yes, turn it.
The person in front of you, yes.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, yes.
I just want to, you know, get the juices flowing a little bit.
Oh!
You mean emulsify oil and water.
So, what do we start with this time?
Yes. First of all, we need to prepare the water for boiling the pasta,
We have 4 liters of water that is boiling on the induction heater over here.
And speaking of boiling pasta,
Salt has to be added,
Salt is very important.
Yes, it's very important.
Here's the point, Miyabizu,
Point!
Add 2% salt! That's it.
Oh!
What's this?
This is for warm, warm food,
It is often said that 1% is the standard,
But the cold one is 2%.
2%?
Wow!
Yes.
Wow! Shines? Put in more than I thought so.
Oh, yeah. When it's cool, you're far from cool.
Now, that's what I'm talking about. While the water boils.
While the water boils, we'll prepare the toppings.
Let's wash the tomatoes a little bit.
How's the group going lately?
How's the group doing these days?
We've been performing at a lot of festivals.
This year alone, we've performed at Lucky Fest, Rock in Japan Fest and Tokyo Idol Fest.
I've had a lot of opportunities to meet other idols.
Is that right?
Yes, it is.
I've realized that there are so many idols from all over the world.
I meet them all behind the scenes.
They are all idols.
Even behind the scenes, they are idols?
That's right.
That's amazing.
But even in the juice department, there are girls who are good at what they do.
What about you?
I'm not good enough.
Then you're the one who has to make the switch.
You're making your debt to me very clear.
Yes, I am.
Let's get this show on the road. - Yes, sir.
Yes, if you're really into it.
I'd like you to cut it in half.
Don't you remove the stems?
I left a little on purpose.
I think it adds interest.
If it goes in easily at first, then it's ready to go.
The skin is a little tough.
I want to separate the peaches for decoration and for the sauce.
Let's do it this way.
I want to keep the curves of the peaches.
I want to cut them like this.
Yes, it's fine.
It looks great at a glance. It makes me feel like a big sister. I'm starting to get it, aren't I?
There's a little more angle to it, isn't there?
Natsuyaki-san told me what she thought of me when we performed together at M-Line Live.
She told me that I looked very mature.
At first...
I didn't talk much.
Were you nervous?
During the rehearsal, she talked a lot.
That's how she seemed.
She seemed like the calm type.
I thought she was...
Not at all. She was outrageous. I was already blown away.
This one is for the sauce, just like the tomatoes.
But you don't say that? Yes, they do.
About seven grains. Seven grains. Seven is my favorite number.
Cut the ham. It was a ham cut.
I heard that you are particular about your solo events.
But there is one burst event a year where you can do everything by yourself, right?
That's where I show off my selfishness.
I am satisfied with doing whatever I want there.
I see. Do you have a set list?
What is the set list?
We decide on a theme every year. I felt I didn't have the ability to deliver the lyrics.
So when I sing, for example, "I love you. I love you,
I think there are two types of people: those who see "I love you" as an emotion, and those who see "I love you" as a word,
I see it as a word. I see it as a word, like "a," "b," "c," "te," and "r." I see it as a Roman letter in my head.
Then I convert them into romaji in my head,
I used to sing in the sense of converting them into roman letters in my head and then putting them into the sound,
But the director told me that I wouldn't be able to reach my feelings if I did that,
I thought to myself, "Sure enough, this is the first year, and last year, between the ages of 18 and 19, I spent a lot of time reading the lyrics,
I spent a lot of time reading the lyrics,
So this year, I focused on lyrics, lyrics that I thought I liked,
So this year, I did a collection of songs with lyrics that I liked and that I wanted to share with my fans, and I did it in Bustelia.
It says 6 minutes, but it could have been a minute more or 2 minutes more for the cold pasta, but I made it 7 minutes and 0 seconds just in case.
Yes, I did.
That's good.
So, let's mix it a little bit.
Yes.
So you are going to put it in ice water.
Into ice water.
Wow, that's great.
Oh, there he is again.
You're being counted.
Yes, I say "wow.
Because today is the first time I know
I've always said I'm amazing.
No kidding?
You're about to tell me.
I didn't realize that.
Really?
Then I brought you some of the stuff I made earlier.
I'm gonna go put it in.
These noodles?
But I love fruit pasta like today's.
I've never had fruit cream pasta before.
It's hard to say.
I've never had it before.
I go to eat there a lot in the summer.
It's stylish.
Like this.
That's great!
Giggle, giggle.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
When you take the salt out, you need to do this.
Giggle. Giggle.
Come on.
Looks good.
It's emulsified perfectly
That's a new one!
I could do it all by myself, like red, red, orange, orange, mom, mom, mom, ham, ham, ham...
I might as well do it.
Okay, I'm satisfied.
There's more.
It smells so good!
Delicious!
It's done!
Chilled pasta with peaches and prosciutto ham is ready.
Yay!
How does it look?
I did the serving, and I think it looks great,
I think it's a perfect score, a hundred points, but what do you think?
It's perfect.
You did it!
Well then, let's try it now.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
How is it?
Delicious!
While you were making it, you mentioned that you made the sour, sweet, and spicy tastes happy, right?
And he did it in a great order, beautifully and clearly.
And his use of the knife was getting better and better.
I think it's going to work.
Nyo!
Please make some for your sisters.
I'll keep this.
Yes, please come visit Hello Kitchen again!
Thank you for your time.
That's all for Hello Kitchen!
Bye-bye!
Let's work together!
This is Sakura Oda and Mariya Makino from Morning Musume。 STE!
From here I would like to tell you a little bit about each other. First of all, I will ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
Yes, I will do my best.
The video of the strongest dance practice version released today is also available. What is the point of the dance?
Self-introduction.
What do you think is the same as when you were a little girl, according to the lyrics of a song about a sentimental time?
Love.
What does summer mean to Mariya Makino?
Sun-baked four sides of the face
What do you think is the most enjoyable moment in your daily life?
What is the most enjoyable moment in your daily life? When I am working as Mariya Makino of Morning Musume。
Currently in the middle of the application period for Halo Project New Member Audition 2024.
What do you remember most from the auditions you participated in?
Sakura Oda.
You mentioned my name when talking about auditions.
I auditioned for the 10th term members and the 11th term members.
During the audition for the 11th term members, I went through to the final screening with Ms. Oda.
At that time, when Mr. Kun Kun asked me a question, he said that it was Oda-chan who didn't sing.
He said that the level was totally different and that she didn't sing or dance.
I'll never forget the shockingly good performance of Oda-san's singing at that time.
I was auditioning a lot, and it's the same story with Maria-chan's mindset.
I'm talking to the kids who are auditioning now, and I'm telling them that it's okay to do so.
I'm talking to the kids who are auditioning now, and I'm saying that it's fine if they are. I've been looking at the girls who became Morning Musume。
I have an image that many of them are like they were destined to become a member of Morning Musume。
So you who are auditioning now, it's not that you want to be accepted or that you want the judges to think you're cute, it's just that you've already been chosen by fate.
It's like you're just auditioning as a part of the process of your destiny, and it's time for you to be found, to be discovered.
amos en la vida
I did try my best, but I didn't really dress up, I just went with it.
It's not a question of what kind of girl will be accepted, but rather, "You'll be accepted, so please come as you are.
Of course, those who are good at singing and dancing are also welcome to apply, and those who have never done it before but want to love it are also welcome.
If you have the desire to become a member of Morning Musume。 I'm sure I could become a member of Morning Musume。 or Hello Project.
There are a lot of voices that say, "Yes, I had confidence and certainty.
It was a strange confidence, wasn't it?
I don't have any evidence to back it up.
It was like, "I'm sure it's going to happen.
I hope you'll have that kind of confidence.
The deadline for auditions is 10:00 a.m. on September 2.
I'm sending mine in at the last minute, the day before the deadline.
You can think about it until the last minute if you want.
I look forward to working with you!
Questions for Mr. Oda will be after the VTR.
Halostei
Morning Musume。24「Something sentimental song
Now on sale
Morning Musume。24最強 Now on sale
Hello! Project New Member Audition 2024
Hello! Project is looking for new members!
Every member of Hello!
The important thing is to have the courage to take the first step.
We will do our best to support your first step!
This time, we will hold auditions in two categories
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project!
If you love singing, dancing, and Hello Project, you should audition in the Hello Project category.
And for those of you who want to show off your skills and personality in addition to singing and dancing
Please apply for the BEYONES Potential Division.
Why don't you join us and make your dreams come true at Hello Project?
We look forward to hearing from you!
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Ms. Oda a question.
What is the most powerful makeup item for this summer?
The most powerful makeup item for this summer is
Colored sunscreen.
What do you do when you want to immerse yourself in a slightly sentimental world?
I listen to dark music.
If you had the whole summer off, how would you spend it?
I would like to meet people I want to meet in my neighborhood.
Please tell us a secret about Sakura Oda that hasn't been revealed to the world yet.
I was actually born underwater.
Last month, I released a photo book, Sakura Flow.
Tell us your interpretation of the word "diva," which is also the theme of your work.
I was faced with the problem of how to create an atmosphere that only comes out on stage, without singing and dancing.
That's all.
First of all, I'd like to ask you about Sakura Oda's photo book Sakuraburo.
Usually, photo books are taken in a natural or casual style, but this time, she wanted to show me in concert.
I'm sure I feel like I'm a different person when I'm on stage.
I feel like a different person when I'm on stage, so it's hard for me to do it in my private life, even if I wanted to.
That's why it's so great to capture that aura in a still photograph.
I fought with him, and I thought that the way he opened his eyes was different from the way I did.
The way you open your eyes is different from the way you open your mouth like on stage.
I was thinking about how to open my eyes like on stage and how to open my mouth like on stage.
Please take a look!
And a secret that hasn't been released to the world yet.
Yes, it's true!
I was born in the water... I was really born in the water.
My mother was soaking in the bathtub with a midwife next to her.
I was born in the bathtub, and the midwife was standing next to me, and she held me up out of the water with a thud.
That's right.
That's how I was born.
But when I think about it, I've never met anyone else who was born in a bathtub.
Yes, Member
I've heard a lot of stories about Mr. Oda, but I've never met anyone else who was born in a bathtub, except for Mr. Oda.
I didn't think I was strange, so I didn't dare to say so, but have you ever met anyone who was born in the water?
I'm wondering if there are people like me who were born underwater... I think we've solved one of the mysteries, Oda-san.
We'll continue with Haloste after this.
I'm Sahara Kawano, a 17 year old high school senior from Fukuoka Prefecture.
I love Hello Project very much.
Hello Project makes me happy when I see them.
I want to bring happiness to many people.
I wanted to bring happiness to many people.
That's why I joined the project.
There are parts I have grown up and parts I haven't.
I have come to understand my own issues clearly.
I think I can do my best from now on.
I think I can play the role of a big sister.
Thank you very much.
I am older than you.
There are a lot of newcomers here.
I teach them things.
I'm like a senior.
I enjoy the rhythm and tempo of the music
I feel happy just listening to them.
They have a gap between the two.
He's very cool and sometimes cute.
I admire the fact that you can do anything.
I watch anime.
I can do things in anime that I can't do in real life.
I like that a lot.
Eating spicy food.
I can eat up to habaneros.
My dream is to make my debut as a member of Hello Project.
I've been told I'm cheerful and energetic.
I think I'm funny.
I think I'm a funny person.
But I can do it alone.
I ask myself questions.
When I say, "It's good, isn't it?", he says, "Hmmm.
Hakata dialect.
Let me say something in Hakata dialect.
It's a canteen.
Here's a canteen.
I'm the head cheerleader for the gymnastics festival. I'm in charge of organizing all the cheerleaders, teaching them how to dance, and deciding where to stand and whatnot.
I want to go to Korea and study Korean.
I would like to go to Korea to study Korean. I would like to go to Korea because the fashion is very cute and they put a lot of effort into beauty.
Thank you very much for watching.
My name is Leopa.
I used to have a Leopa.
She's got big eyes, and she's very comforting.
I love reptiles.
When I decided I wanted to get a reptile, I fell in love with her and got her.
I had snakes and chameleons and all kinds of things.
I didn't keep snakes because they bite.
But my father was bitten by one, and I just looked at it.
I thought they were cute, and I saw them drinking water, and I thought they were cute.
I thought they were cute.
I'm going to try playing kendama, a game I've been good at lately.
Thank you for watching.
I have a lot of regrets.
I couldn't do it well.
I didn't have confidence at that time.
I went out on stage with no confidence.
I really regret it.
I don't have much confidence.
I'm not so confident now, but I'm determined to do my best.
I want to learn how to breathe and how to be strong.
I want to start all over again and relearn how to breathe.
I want to become as good as all the trainees.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Thank you for watching!
This time, we have Sora Kono, a trainee from Morning Musume。
There was a time when Morning Musume。24 performed at the Hallopro trainee presentation.
I sang all the songs together with the trainees, and Sora-chan sang with me.
I sang with Sora-chan.
The part... The part...
It's so nice to see you two in such a gorgeous lineup.
Soar-chan was so cute too.
Hey!
I sang the lyrics "Born on a star that I love", thinking that's exactly what Soara was thinking.
Soara-chan is tall, even among the trainees, she stands out, and she's a senior.
That's why we don't feel like you have to be a big sister.
So I'm looking forward to seeing you make the most of your youthfulness and your pure cuteness, and become more and more active in the future.
I think Maria and I felt the same way at the presentation of the trainees, but...
I think Maria and I felt the same way at the presentation of the trainees. I wanted to show them that we haven't changed, that we're still the same.
I'm sorry, but we were standing on stage as if we were going to stand out.
I remember I recorded it because it was my original song, and when we were performing the kulaing, Mr. Tsunku called all the trainees and asked them how they were feeling.
When we were performing the Kulaing, Mr. Tsunku talked about how he felt when he called all the trainees together. I remember that I recorded it because it was an original piece.
I danced. I was a member of Morning Musume。 I was a Morning Musume member at the time of Climax.
I was the only one who sang on the edit sheet, but I think the original six members sang in "Kanojo ni naritai" as well.
I was in the original six members of Morning Musume。 I took one dance lesson and performed the song "Chaser" at the presentation of the trainees.
Yes, that was my first performance of "I want to be her.
I was so happy to be able to do it.
Please look forward to the next episode of Halo Pro Trainee Corner!
This episode is presented by Sakura Oda and Mariya Makino from Morning Musume。 24.
As I mentioned at the beginning, Morning Musume。 2474th single "Nandaka sentimental na toki no uta saikou" was released on August 14, the day of this distribution!
How was the recording of the song?
The recording of "Saikyou no Uta Saikyou" was done by a director for the first time.
Project's director for the first time.
Project's concerts and so on.
So the director tried to get to know the members and took pictures of us.
Are you good at various things? Is he a clumsy person? He asked me if I was good at what I do or not.
The most dexterous.
We talked about how dexterous you are with your hands while recording.
I was asked if I am a dexterous person. But...
But there are times when I'm not so good at it.
When you sing in a sentimental way, the song is really different.
The songs are really different.
And when Tsunku himself wrote the song
Tsunku himself said that when he wrote the song, he thought "How am I going to sing this song without unison?
He said that at first, he didn't want to have any unison.
He even thought about ending the song with all solos.
It's like...
I guess it's hard to connect the solo parts because it's so personal, and Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。ヌs is good at connecting the solo parts, so I thought it was a song that only Morning Musume。ヌs could do. I thought it was a song that could only be sung by Morning Musume。
Tsunku himself said that each member sang a solo part at the birthday event, and that it would be nice if each member had their own version of the song.
We usually record parts of the song, but since we sing the whole song at once, it's very different.
I think it's because the members don't have the same melody or anything that makes me hungry.
I think the interpretation of this song is something that the older I get, the more I remember it. There's a 10 to 12 age difference between the two groups right now.
I mean, there's an age gap of 10 or 12 this year, and Ako-chan, the youngest member who came out with the bow, said she really couldn't relate to it at all, and I thought she hadn't grown up yet.
She said that she is happy every day, that she is good at smiling, and that she never gets tired of talking to people.
Then she said that she could tell about half the age of Rio Sakurai and Mei Yamazaki, who are somewhere in the middle.
So you are gradually getting to know them?
That's right.
They must be older than you.
That's right, and I can't quite identify with them.
Me too.
That's why I've grown up.
I don't even know what this song means anymore.
But the other day I asked an adult staff member about it, and he said there was a time when he thought about things like this song.
So you're saying there's more to it than that?
There are people who have gone beyond that.
So maybe it's a good thing that you can relate to this... Tomorrow, August 15, there will be a release celebration event at Shinagawa Intercity Hall.
So please come to this event and listen to the song and the most powerful song of the time, "Kind of Sentimental".
Please take a moment to think about the meaning of both songs.
If you can listen to them while thinking about the meaning of the songs, I think you will enjoy our performance even more.
Morning Musume。 2474th single, a song about a somewhat sentimental time, the strongest Please listen to it a lot!
Please listen to it a lot!
Do you love me? Don't you love me?
Side Mirror Machi ha Sway
I don't love you, but I love you Tokyo, tonight it's going to overflow
Radio Caravelle, it's gonna rain tomorrow.
You knew that, didn't you? Why are you doing that?
Love and Joy at Dawn
Go ahead, change it.
Hello to take away
Sleepless in love
Get out of the room seat
With a new me
Let's go see a new morning
Prajumation
The back of the room is whispering
Why wind
plastic plastic plastic sember base
I love you
Say I love you
I love you on the wings, my longing is warm
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I don't love you, I love you somehow
Makery GPS Beyond Por Prado
empresas santas
Nobody иск Prophet
default
Może
But
You're not so bad.
The sound of excitement. You gave me your body.
You gave me your hands.
I can't go to hell, I can't stop breathing
Help me, help me, love enjoy in profile
Someday I'm Leaning Toward You
monocall discussing with kindness
I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk, I'm drunk
as many as the number of galaxies
Tear grass that becomes a bond
Graduation, it wasn't you
Dyeing Phenomenon
I can't help it, I can't help it, I can't help it
I'm still drunk on the noise
when will I crush you tomorrow
Aiming for the first star
Temptation, Predictable Love Enjoyment
Here, change it for me
Rubal Hand Sleepless Love
Get out of the passenger seat
Lubal Hand, my heart
No one can ever be wrong at all
So a little tear or a little
To blot
in the days of Misifin
tile
three cars
Deixa
탄
ten
sink
. \cHB9C09}
viewer
You did a great job, take a good rest.
Morning Musume。24Oda Sakura and
Mariaki Makino, who is a member of Morning Musume。 STE, presented by Sakura Oda and Mariami Makino.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here's an announcement!
Our new single "Kind of Sentimental Toki no Uta Saikyou" will be released
It will be released today, the day of distribution!
Tomorrow at Shinagawa Intercity Hall
There will be a mini-live & farewell party to celebrate the release!
Hello Project 2024 Summer All of Us Vega Altael is underway!
This weekend, we will have a concert in Fukuoka.
Morning Musume。24 Concert Tour Autumn We Can Dance will start on September 14!
Please come and see us!
On September 22, Morning Musume。24 will perform at Rock in Japan Festival 2024 in Hitachinaka.
Morning Musume。24 will perform!
Hello Project New Member Audition 2024 is now underway, and we are accepting applications in two categories: Hello Project Audition is for girls from 5th grade to 16 years old, and Hello Project Audition is for girls from 5th grade to 16 years old.
The Diones Potential audition is for girls from high school freshman to 20 years old.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will appear more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel.
Our partners were Sakura Oda of Morning Musume。 24 and Marie Nanaki.
Goodbye.
Thank you for watching.